
var stims_1_primed =[{"id":"presents","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got about   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get about   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built between   70  and  80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed between   70  and  80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, more than   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received more than   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that at least   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are at least   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Are there some seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up some chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has she published any articles in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written any articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are    40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant    40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are about   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have about   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated between   15  and  20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for between   15  and  20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, more than   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made more than   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains at least   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't at least   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Have some absentee ballots already been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received some absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have any copies of the agenda for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed any copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered    8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made    8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_2_primed =[{"id":"builders","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built about   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed about   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, between   20  and  30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received between   20  and  30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that more than   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't more than   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, at least   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up at least   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has she also published some articles in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written some articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there any space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant any tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are    20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have    20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated about   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for about   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, between   50  and  60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made between   50  and  60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains more than   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were more than   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that at least   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received at least   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have some copies of the agenda for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed some copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked any cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made any chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got    15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got    15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_3_primed =[{"id":"jobposting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, about   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received about   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that between   30  and  40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are between   30  and  40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, more than   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up more than   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published at least   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written at least   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there some space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant some tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have any tickets become available for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have any tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated    20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for    20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, about   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made about   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains between   5  and  10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't between   5  and  10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that more than   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received more than   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, at least   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed at least   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked some cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made some chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Did her classmate Timmy get any presents from his relatives?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get any presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built    80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed    80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_4_primed =[{"id":"algebra","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that about   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't about   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, between   14  and  16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up between   14  and  16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published more than   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written more than   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are at least   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant at least   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have some tickets become available for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have some tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have any money in our budget to pay for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for any scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,    60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made    60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains about   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were about   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that between   150  and  200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received between   150  and  200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, more than   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed more than   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered at least   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made at least   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Did her classmate Timmy get some presents from his relatives?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got some presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Has the company completed any houses this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed any houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,    30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received    30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_5_primed =[{"id":"chairs","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, about   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up about   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published between   10  and  15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written between   10  and  15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are more than   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant more than   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are at least   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have at least   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have some money in our budget to pay for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for some scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked any hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made any hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains    10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't    10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that about   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received about   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, between   15  and  20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed between   15  and  20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered more than   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made more than   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got at least   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get at least   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Has the company also completed some houses this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed some houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"Has anyone applied so far to the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received any applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that    40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are    40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_6_primed =[{"id":"journalist","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published about   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written about   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are more than   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have more than   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated at least   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for at least   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked some hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made some hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Did Connor's exam paper have any misspelled words?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were any spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that    200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received    200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, about   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed about   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered between   6  and  8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made between   6  and  8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got more than   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got more than   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built at least   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed at least   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"Have some people already applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received some applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Have any sophomores registered so far?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't any sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,    16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up    16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_7_primed =[{"id":"tulips","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are about   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant about   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are between   15  and  20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have between   15  and  20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated more than   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for more than   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, at least   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made at least   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Did Connor's exam paper have some misspelled words?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't some spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Have any absentee ballots been mailed in so far?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received any absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,    20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed    20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered about   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made about   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got between   10  and  15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get between   10  and  15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built more than   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed more than   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, at least   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received at least   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Have some sophomores already registered?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are some sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Are there any seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up any chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published    15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written    15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_8_primed =[{"id":"tickets","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are about   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have about   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated between   15  and  20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for between   15  and  20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, more than   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made more than   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains at least   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were at least   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Have some absentee ballots already been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received some absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have any copies of the agenda for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed any copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered    8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made    8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got about   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got about   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built between   70  and  80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed between   70  and  80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, more than   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received more than   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that at least   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't at least   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Are there some seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up some chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has she published any articles in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written any articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are    40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant    40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_9_primed =[{"id":"nominees","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated about   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for about   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, between   50  and  60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made between   50  and  60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains more than   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't more than   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that at least   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received at least   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have some copies of the agenda for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed some copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked any cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made any chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got    15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get    15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built about   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed about   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, between   20  and  30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received between   20  and  30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that more than   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are more than   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, at least   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up at least   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has she also published some articles in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written some articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there any space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant any tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are    20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have    20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_10_primed =[{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, about   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made about   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains between   5  and  10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were between   5  and  10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that more than   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received more than   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, at least   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed at least   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked some cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made some chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Did her classmate Timmy get any presents from his relatives?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got any presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built    80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed    80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, about   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received about   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that between   30  and  40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't between   30  and  40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, more than   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up more than   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published at least   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written at least   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there some space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant some tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have any tickets become available for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have any tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated    20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for    20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_11_primed =[{"id":"exam","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains about   10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't about   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that between   150  and  200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received between   150  and  200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, more than   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed more than   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered at least   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made at least   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Did her classmate Timmy get some presents from his relatives?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get some presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Has the company completed any houses this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed any houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,    30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received    30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that about   40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are about   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, between   14  and  16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up between   14  and  16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published more than   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written more than   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are at least   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant at least   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have some tickets become available for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have some tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have any money in our budget to pay for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for any scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,    60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made    60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_12_primed =[{"id":"voting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that about   200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received about   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, between   15  and  20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed between   15  and  20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered more than   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made more than   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got at least   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got at least   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Has the company also completed some houses this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed some houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"Has anyone applied so far to the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received any applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that    40 sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Are the registrations in line with what we expected?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't    40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening, about   16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up about   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published between   10  and  15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written between   10  and  15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are more than   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant more than   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are at least   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have at least   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have some money in our budget to pay for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for some scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked any hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made any hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains    10 misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Will Connor's exam paper need to be rewritten?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were    10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_13_primed =[{"id":"delegates","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon, about   20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't printed about   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered between   6  and  8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The baker has made between   6  and  8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got more than   15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> Timmy didn't get more than   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built at least   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The company has constructed at least   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"Have some people already applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received some applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Have any sophomores registered so far?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There are any sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,    16 committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Do we have enough seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't set up    16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published about   15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> The journalist has written about   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have space to plant between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are more than   20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have more than   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated at least   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have the money for at least   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked some hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've made some hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Did Connor's exam paper have any misspelled words?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There weren't any spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that    200 overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Is that how many absentee ballots have been mailed in?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received    200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_14_primed =[{"id":"cakes","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The hotel has ordered about   8 large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"Have we baked enough cakes to fill their order?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The baker hasn't made about   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got between   10  and  15 presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"Was her classmate Timmy equally lucky?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> Timmy got between   10  and  15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"Last year, the construction company built more than   80 houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"Is the company's performance similar this year?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The company hasn't constructed more than   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening, at least   30 people applied from all over the country","question":"Are we seeing similar results for the currently advertised job?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've received at least   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"Have some sophomores already registered?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> There aren't some sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"Are there any seats in the meeting room?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've set up any chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The famous journalist has published    15 in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"Has her work appeared as often in The Washington Post?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> The journalist hasn't written    15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are about   40 tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"Is there space to plant them in the garden?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have space to plant about   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"There are between   15  and  20 people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"Have tickets become available for all of them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We don't have between   15  and  20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The teachers have nominated more than   20 promising students to receive scholarships","question":"Do we have enough money in our budget to cover that many?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We have the money for more than   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"In two weeks, at least   60 regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"Have we booked hotel rooms for them?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't made at least   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"Did Connor's exam paper have some misspelled words?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> There were some spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"Have any absentee ballots been mailed in so far?","response":"<\/b>No. <b> We haven't received any absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"primed","setup":"This afternoon,    20 delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"Do we have enough copies of the agenda for them? ","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b> We've printed    20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_1_neutral =[{"id":"presents","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get about   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed between   70  and  80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received more than   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are at least   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up some chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written any articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant    40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have about   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for between   15  and  20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made more than   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't at least   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received some absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed any copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":1,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made    8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_2_neutral =[{"id":"builders","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed about   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received between   20  and  30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't more than   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up at least   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written some articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant any tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have    20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for about   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made between   50  and  60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were more than   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received at least   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed some copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made any chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":2,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got    15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_3_neutral =[{"id":"jobposting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received about   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are between   30  and  40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up more than   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written at least   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant some tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have any tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for    20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made about   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't between   5  and  10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received more than   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed at least   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made some chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get any presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":3,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed    80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_4_neutral =[{"id":"algebra","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't about   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up between   14  and  16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written more than   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant at least   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have some tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for any scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made    60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were about   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received between   150  and  200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed more than   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made at least   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got some presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed any houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":4,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received    30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_5_neutral =[{"id":"chairs","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up about   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written between   10  and  15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant more than   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have at least   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for some scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made any hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't    10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received about   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed between   15  and  20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made more than   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get at least   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed some houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received any applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":5,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are    40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_6_neutral =[{"id":"journalist","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written about   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have more than   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for at least   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made some hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were any spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received    200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed about   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made between   6  and  8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got more than   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed at least   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received some applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't any sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":6,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up    16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_7_neutral =[{"id":"tulips","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant about   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have between   15  and  20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for more than   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made at least   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't some spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received any absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed    20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made about   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get between   10  and  15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed more than   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received at least   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are some sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up any chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":7,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written    15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_8_neutral =[{"id":"tickets","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have about   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for between   15  and  20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made more than   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were at least   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received some absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed any copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made    8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got about   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed between   70  and  80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received more than   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't at least   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up some chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written any articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":8,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant    40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_9_neutral =[{"id":"nominees","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for about   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made between   50  and  60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't more than   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received at least   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed some copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made any chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get    15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed about   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received between   20  and  30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are more than   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up at least   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written some articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant any tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":9,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have    20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_10_neutral =[{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made about   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were between   5  and  10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received more than   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed at least   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made some chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got any presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed    80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received about   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't between   30  and  40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up more than   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written at least   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant some tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have any tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":10,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for    20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_11_neutral =[{"id":"exam","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't about   10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received between   150  and  200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed more than   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made at least   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get some presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed any houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received    30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are about   40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up between   14  and  16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written more than   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant at least   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have some tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for any scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":11,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made    60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_12_neutral =[{"id":"voting","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received about   200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed between   15  and  20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made more than   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got at least   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed some houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received any applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't    40 sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up about   16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written between   10  and  15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant more than   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have at least   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for some scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made any hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":12,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were    10 spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_13_neutral =[{"id":"delegates","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We haven't printed about   20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"cakes","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker has made between   6  and  8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy didn't get more than   15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company has constructed at least   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We haven't received some applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There are any sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We haven't set up    16 chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist has written about   15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We don't have space to plant between   30  and  40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We have more than   20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We don't have the money for at least   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We've made some hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There weren't any spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":13,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We've received    200 absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

var stims_14_neutral =[{"id":"cakes","expr":"about","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The hotel has ordered  large chocolate cakes for the party tonight","question":"How many cakes have we baked so far?","response":"The baker hasn't made about   8 chocolate cakes","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"presents","expr":"between","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This year at Christmas, Suzy got  presents from her aunts, uncles and cousins","question":"How much did her classmate Timmy get?","response":"Timmy got between   10  and  15 presents from his relatives","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"builders","expr":"morethan","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"Last year, the construction company built  houses in California, Arizona and Nevada","question":"How has the company's performance been this year?","response":"The company hasn't constructed more than   80 houses this year","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"jobposting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The last time we advertised a job opening,  people applied from all over the country","question":"How many people have applied to the currently advertised job?","response":"We've received at least   30 applications","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"algebra","expr":"some","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"We predicted that  sophomores would register for the advanced algebra class","question":"How many sophomores have registered so far?","response":"There aren't some sophomores registered for the class","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"chairs","expr":"any","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This evening,  committee members will be coming for the planning meeting","question":"How many seats are there in the meeting room?","response":"We've set up any chairs in the meeting room","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"journalist","expr":"bare","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The famous journalist has published  in-depth articles in The New York Times","question":"How often has her work appeared in The Washington Post?","response":"The journalist hasn't written    15 articles for The Washington Post","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tulips","expr":"about","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  tulip bulbs in the bag we bought at the nursery","question":"How much space is there to plant them in the garden?","response":"We have space to plant about   40 tulip bulbs","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"tickets","expr":"between","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"There are  people on the waiting list for tonight's concert","question":"How many tickets have become available?","response":"We don't have between   15  and  20 tickets available","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"nominees","expr":"morethan","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The teachers have nominated  promising students to receive scholarships","question":"How many scholarships can our budget cover?","response":"We have the money for more than   20 scholarships","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"salesmeeting","expr":"atleast","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"In two weeks,  regional employees will be flying to company headquarters for the annual sales meeting","question":"How many hotel rooms have we booked for them?","response":"We haven't made at least   60 hotel reservations","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"exam","expr":"some","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"If a student's exam paper contains  misspelled words, it may need to be rewritten","question":"How many misspelled words were there in Connor's exam paper?","response":"There were some spelling errors in his exam","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"voting","expr":"any","polarity":"negative","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"The Board of Elections predicted that  overseas voters would vote by mail","question":"How many absentee ballots have been mailed in so far?","response":"We haven't received any absentee ballots","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"delegates","expr":"bare","polarity":"positive","list":14,"primetype":"neutral","setup":"This afternoon,  delegates will be arriving to attend the convention","question":"How many copies of the agenda do we have for them?","response":"We've printed    20 copies of the agenda","type":"critical","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}]

